Have you ever thought about having a content feedback system to where you send o
on social media, you get the URL, you wait a little bit, you get the analytics t
done well or done good, Then you didn't take that post analytics, The post detai
status, data, transcript, all those other images, and then you now categorize it
bad, And you contrast that with the analytics to say whether it is good or bad
bad, And you contrast that with the analytics to say whether it is good or bad b
because it didn't make any people view the video, it didn't get that engagement,
And then now you have, you put that, result into AI. So I'm talking about AI
And then now you have, you put that, result into AI. So I'm talking about AI sol
solution. I don't know how this might fit for you or it may fit for other people
an AI solution that can be wrapped up in many different things based on your typ
what you to put out there, And you have this AI solution is now, take that
what you to put out there, And you have this AI solution is now, take that data,
data, you multiply this data over time, you now are, training AI itself to
then be able to point out bad pieces of content and sort them out from the good
And also, you can also, feedback that system back into your inputs of your conte
process. And then now you can have, increasingly better and better content,
process. And then now you can have, increasingly better and better content, And
And this is what people are doing in 2026. And this is what I want to show you h